The End.
The End. The End.
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music!
We share the music!
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one dream!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the good times!
We share the good times!
Let's go, baby, baby,
always share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see or to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go, one straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Always share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Always share the one world.
Just watch.
Okay.
I'll show you what I can
do when I go all out.
Now second gear.
What's he doing now?
Is it me or is he steaming?
Men are kind of scary, aren't they?
They're nothing like us, that's for sure.
In other words, boy, all your little
trick has done is awaken our wrath.
Medusa here!
Eight-headed serpent!
We love you, Sandusonia!
She bit through the fence!
Even though the snakes are
just made out of her hair,
those fangs hit as hard as iron!
Why can't I hit him?
I know what he's going to do, but
somehow I still can't keep up!
Come, come!
Don't bother.
As you've clearly seen before, your
attacks simply bounce off of them.
me.
Let's find out.
Check out.
Sonia, Mary.
If I recall, you were supposed to kill
the man, not indulge in his foolish games.
But...
but sister...
His transgressions are,
in a word, unforgivable.
I refuse to tolerate him any longer.
Yes, of course we're very sorry, sister.
We'll finish him immediately.
Whoa!
She's on fire!
Medusa here!
Salamander!
There's nowhere left to run, man!
If he doesn't get bitten, he's
gonna get burned for sure!
Ooh, this is my favorite attack!
Now come, come!
Jack!
No, Sonya!
I didn't mean to!
Hurry, get away from me!
Something is dragging me closer!
Our tail! How did he?
I'm burning!
Sonia, stop!
You're fooling me!
Watch out, Sonia! Don't fall!
That's the pit of blades!
Hold on to the stands!
Whoa, that was close!
Thunder, Sonia, no!
He's going to knock her
down and skewer her.
Isn't winning enough you animal?
Do you have to kick her
while she's down too?
Are you here to mock me? Don't move.
Even if you guys want to kill me.
That doesn't mean that I want to kill you.
Why of all the insolent?
Mary, this is your
chance to finish him off.
Don't just stand there. Hurry.
I can't, don't you understand?
He isn't mocking you, sister.
That man is!
Protecting us.
Oh no, Sandersonia's clothing
burned off in the fire.
Her back is showing.
If he gets off her, her
gorgon eyes will be exposed.
Hurry, look away, she's going
to turn us all to stone!
I didn't even realize.
It's like your sister said before, right?
What you saw is a secret we
would die to protect Or rather,
one that we would kill to protect
in this particular instance.
You'd rather die than let people
see this thing on your back, right?
Like I said, don't move.
This match is hereby over.
Everyone, you must
leave the arena at once.
Do not gaze upon the Gorgon eyes.
Get out of here! Get away!
You know that I was trying to
kill you just a moment ago.
Why are you protecting me?
Because that mark on your back
has nothing to do with our fight.
We can always settle things later.
If you truly want to move
forward in this world,
You must come to terms with
what you wear on your back?
Please forgive us, Hancock.
We lost and were rescued by our enemy
Okay, what now you next?
We're done.
I'm not in the mood to fight.
Really, is she okay?
No cracks.
So you're gonna fix them, right?
Make them normal again.
You heard me.
You can make them normal, right?
Can't you?
It's not like they did anything wrong.
They just told the truth!
Come on, please!
Of course I can.
I can easily reverse the
effects if I choose to do so.
But, to be clear, didn't you say
you wanted to go somewhere by ship?
Yeah, I gotta get back and find my crew.
I see.
I have bad news.
You must decide.
I can either return them to normal,
or help you to reach your destination.
Choose one, forget the other.
That's all I'm willing to do.
Now we'll see your true nature.
Good deal! That's great!
Well, okay, go ahead and turn him back!
Seriously!
Thank you!
That man,
he has such an immensely powerful Haki,
but didn't hesitate to save those he owes.
Incredible.
Hey, look at Margaret. Sweet pea.
And, uh, Philandra.
Hey, everyone.
I was wondering where you went.
How wonderful.
She reversed the petrification.
I was so worried.
I just couldn't believe it
when you defended that man.
None of us could.
And then you were turned to stone.
It was awful. Stone? Huh?
Huh?
Uh, what happened to us?
Most peculiar.
I have no recollection.
You can't remember a thing? No.
I came to, and the man,
well, he seemed so happy.
Oh, this is great.
I was really freaking out there.
I thought you guys were going to die.
Where did everyone go?
Is the trial over?
That's all I can remember.
It's fine.
You're not the first to have trouble
remembering after you've been turned to stone.
Don't worry I'll catch you up on
the details of what happened later,
but what did happen and what
did she do with the man?
You really need to ask?
She just turned him to stone
and got on with her day.
Well, I could be mistaken, but it looked
like they took him to Kuja Castle?
Hey, what'd you say you want from me? Oh,
please tell me you're
gonna serve up a big after
battle Meal for us so what's
the best food around here?
Some kind of meat?
Just so you know, I'm
grateful. For what you did?
Thank you.
Forget it. It was nothing. Really.
Feed me and we'll call it even.
If anyone had seen what's on our backs,
it would have been the end of us.
We'd be cast out, never to return.
You may enter. Hmm.
I said, come inside.
Where?
Behind the curtain.
Oh, you got the food? Back there?
Here?
I
Hey, where's the food and how
come you took your clothes off?
My astute and charming, aren't you?
Look,
the mark on my back.
You.
You said you said that
you'd seen it before.
I need to know.
Take a closer look.
Where have you seen it?
Do you know what this mark means?
Answer me! Hurry up!
This isn't pleasant, you know.
It's not the same, but it still
reminds me of the one I've seen before.
There's this friend of mine.
He's a fish man, and his name is Hachi.
He's got a mark kind of like that one
on his forehead, but it's different.
I've never seen one like yours.
If he doesn't know what it is, tell him.
Granny, why are you here?
Snake Princess, be honest.
You know you can trust him by now.
You've seen with your
own eyes he's a good man.
Go ahead, child.
Do not fear.
Your secret is safe.
You, you're the notorious pirate
known as Monkey D. Luffy, correct?
Yeah, that's me.
How do you know anything about me?
You do seem like a decent enough
young man, despite your reputation.
Take a look at this newspaper.
Just a few days before he arrived, he caused
an incident on the Sabaori Archipelago.
An incident with dire repercussions.
Not only did he oppose the Celestial
Dragons, he punched one of them.
You must be insane.
By some miracle,
he was able to escape the Central
Forces they unleashed to capture him.
And just as miraculous,
he traveled from that faraway
location to here in a few short days.
Both of these things are
beyond my comprehension.
I told you, remember?
I got flung here.
Honestly, I don't even know where we are.
I've never heard of it.
And I don't feel one bit bad about
knocking out that celestial dragon
Does that newspaper even mention
what that bastard did to my friend?
Then it's true?
Are you telling me that you
actually struck a celestial dragon?
I'm amazed.
I truly had no idea.
That there could be such a
wonderful fool left in this world?
To challenge the world nobles.
and risk your life?
You're just like he was.
Yes.
I will tell you everything
there is to know.
I can even tell you why your fishman friend
has that emblem, and also what it means.
Ah, jeez, Mark.
This brand is...
The Claw of the Celestial Dragon.
The Emblem of the World Nobles.
The celestial dragons branded
upon those they take as slaves.
A marking to steal your humanity and claim
you as their property and they marked you.
You see the three of
us were my sisters and
I we were once slaves of the world nobles.
It happened when I was 12 years old.
You hungry?
I brought a snack out for you.
Hey, Hancock! Sonia! Mary!
Where are you?
The three of us were abducted
from a Kuja pirate ship.
In broad daylight, no less.
And then we were sold.
From that point on, we were submitted
to a hell we can never forget.
The first men we ever encountered were
nothing but figures of cruelty and horror.
Sonia, it'll be okay!
The memories will always haunt us.
Hey, don't put yourself through this!
I've heard enough!
Really!
Please, don't keep going!
It was all so awful.
Our world was naught but despair.
And we prayed for the mercy of death.
Hey, come on!
But, after four years of that misery,
there came a night that shocked even
the world government to its core.
It was accepted as a rule
of the world that no one
would ever dare challenge
the Celestial Dragons.
But on that fateful night,
there was a man who
scaled the red line with
his bare hands and slipped into Merijoie,
the holy land of the Celestial Dragons.
This man was an adventurer who later
led the fishman pirates, Fisher Tiger.
He arrived with the sole
purpose of releasing
his fellow fishmen who suffered as slaves.
He wreaked havoc on the
world nobles without reserve.
We're free!
Despite his hatred for
humans as a species!
He freed every one of us.
saving thousands of slaves
regardless of who or what they were.
And so we fled, more than
willing to risk death.
We owe an eternal debt to Fisher Tiger.
In the end, tiger unleashed an army.
Fishmen swarmed the oceans.
But they were cursed to wear the
celestial dragon's mark of slavery.
Tiger was relentlessly hunted
by the world government.
So he brought the fugitives together
to form the pirates of the sun.
And sailed far and wide across the seas.
In order to erase the last
trace of their bondage.
The former slaves made a new brand
over the claw of the Celestial Dragon.
Changing them into a symbol of the sun.
There you have it.
By necessity, my brand bears
a similarity in design.
That's why you mistook it for the
symbol of the sun pirates before.
Yeah, guess so.
The mark on Hachi's forehead
does look like a sun.
Wait, does that mean
Hachi used to be a slave?
Possibly, although not necessarily.
Not all of Tiger's pirates
were former slaves,
but they were all branded with the
symbol to hide their comrades past.
Which is why,
former slave or not,
it's safe to assume that your friend must
have sailed with the Sun
Pirates at some point?
Fisher Tiger has been
dead for some time now.
Upon his passing, the Sun Pirates
disbanded and split into several factions.
Where did you get that wound on your head?
Oh, that.
Don't worry about it, okay?
Now that you know the history of the Mark,
I hope you can better
understand our position.
Yeah, I think I get it.
It's sick.
The things that they made us do as slaves.
They forced me to eat the love-love fruit,
and forced my sisters to eat
snake-snake fruits for their amusement.
Ironically, this allowed us to
hide our secret from the Kuja.
They praise our powers because
they misunderstand them.
But if you hadn't covered
Sandersonia's back in the arena,
the ugly truth would be apparent to them.
I can't stand for anyone
to know of our past.
And I shall make any
sacrifice to ensure that.
Even if I must deceive my own people
I won't let anyone control us again.
I fear my own subjects I can't let anyone
come close to me or they
might know the truth.
Sister
Well, on the bright side of things,
it's been years since
you've displayed even
the most faint affectation of an emotion!
But I welcome your tears as they prove our
sweet snake princess's
heart has not frozen over.
You mock me?
You're the one who left this nation
behind that's neither here nor there
have you already forgotten where you
would be without me yes you escaped the
celestial dragons but you neglected
to mention that you didn't know how to
get home tell me would you have seen
amazon lily again if i hadn't gone to
the outer seas you would have starved
to death hiding in the cracks of the
red line if it wasn't for me a small
kindness you'll never let us forget what
did you say i've watched over the
three of you as though you were my own
daughter yes i suppose you find me
repulsive now that you know i was a slave
really i told you i hate
the celestial dragons
i've decided i like you you said
that there was somewhere you needed
to go yes well my ship's at your
command name the
place well it can
be any kind of boat as long as it
floats we will set sail tomorrow
morning the kuja pirates will get you
safely to the Sabo odi archipelago
with our ship hope it's
no trouble rest well
tonight as i'm sure this
visit has proved taxing
i'll be out of here tomorrow morning
Come on! You can do it! It's like this!
Watch!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
You got it!
Oh, Loopy!
You're hilarious!
That's the chopsticks from
their nose to their mouth!
I'm holding baskets!
How shameful.
Do they have no class at all?
I'm going to tell it to!
It's the specialty of Maiden Island.
Pretty good, what is it?
It's Pinay Gorgonzola with
the meat of a sea king.
I really hope you like it.
I've had sea king before,
but this tastes different.
I like it.
Wow, it really does stretch.
It's soft and squishy like rubber.
Time's up, step aside!
Come on, just a little longer!
No, bad enough!
You can eat it really good.
And it's hard to eat, though?
What the heck are you doing? Cut it out!
I can't eat with you
pulling my face around.
Sorry, we can't help it!
I mean, you're leaving tomorrow, right?
There are a lot of people
here who want to touch you.
Just once.
Look, you're really popular!
Hi, Lucy.
I can't wait to touch you.
You can't just start a
business behind my back!
Come on, Loopy, please!
Tonight is the only chance
we have to touch a man!
No, this is annoying!
I can't even you pushing
me around like this!
I want food not touching!
Where did my freak go?
Hey, where's the man?
Did he run away?
He couldn't have gotten far. Move out!
Let's find him and touch him!
What the heck's the matter with them?
Keep it down.
This was all the food I could
grab before I flew out of there.
It's wonderful you'll be
with your friends soon.
Bet you can't wait.
You said it.
Anyway, I'm sorry for all the
trouble I started while I was here.
I was real worried when
you turned to stone.
But then you protected
all of us, didn't you?
Back in the arena.
I heard all about it.
You're my hero.
Thanks.
Granny Nyon.
Yes, Parker, is something wrong?
No, but the villagers
wouldn't stop touching Luffy.
So I brought him here.
Ah, well it's not every
day they see a man.
Hey, Granny Bean.
He's welcome to stay here
until things die down.
And my name's not Bean.
It seems he has plenty to eat already.
Just bring him some tea.
Okay.
So, Granny, you like reading newspapers?
The cool news isn't delivered anywhere
inside of a comm belt, so it's hard to get.
But there are certain perks when your
empress is one of the seven warlords.
Even with our isolation, I like
knowing what's going on in the world.
Wait a second.
Who's the warlord?
The snake, princess.
What?
She's one of the warlords?
So does that mean she's
actually super strong?
You're a pirate, surely you
know who all the warlords are?
Yeah, he thinks so, huh?
Ugh, don't you ever read a newspaper?
Nope, I sure don't.
Ugh, wow!
The Snake Princess was
crowned ruler of this country,
and she was also named the captain of
the Kuja Pirates around 11 years ago.
She was still young and inexperienced,
but the world government put a bounty
of 80 million berries on her head?
after just one expedition.
What did she do?
The Kaido pirates were notorious
before she became a captain.
Because of that, the world government took
an interest in her right from the start,
which led to their decision to
invite her to become a warlord.
But now her title is about to be revoked.
Since you don't read the papers,
perhaps you haven't heard.
What?
The warlords are teaming
up with the Marines?
And they're going to have a war
with Whitebeard and his crew?
When? How?
This, this is way too much
for me to take in all at once.
What a foolish man you are.
You don't know anything, do you?
Now, listen, that was only
conjecture at this point.
I don't have any proof, but I'd say
that battle is a high probability.
The world government
has laid out their bait,
But Captain Whitebeard would
never ever allow his mates
to be killed But even with
that knowledge They have
announced the public
execution of Port Custee Ace A
powerful and high-ranking
commander in his crew Ace!
A .K .A.
Firefist Ace
They're gonna execute.
According to this, a pirate
named Blackbeard defeated Ace.
and gave him up to the world government.
In return, they invited
him to be a warlord.
Blackbeard, huh?
This sends a strong message.
The government has
caught a big fish indeed.
But more than that,
if this show of authority can prove that
they're stronger than Whitebeard himself,
well...
Granny!
He's just my brother!
Por Castilles, the Fire Fist!
You're talking about my brother!
What?
My word! I never knew!
Yeah, and I didn't know
anything about this.
He's gonna be killed?
But he can still escape, right?
Well, I'd say that his best chance would
be if Whitebeard takes the bait and wins.
Tell me, does it say where
they're gonna execute him?
In the town square of Marineford,
where Navy Headquarters is located.
It says the execution will
take place in one week.
That's six days from today
That's too soon!
How long will it take to get
from here back to Sabo Odi?
Even at top speed, it would
take more than a week!
A week!
That means by the time
I meet up with my crew?
It'd be too late.
He's would already be dead.
Yes How long to get to where
Aces well if he's being held at
Impel down that would take I
would say a week on a pirate ship
Perhaps four days on a
Navy ship. Whoa, wait!
Since when are Navy ships that fast?
There's a sea current that's reserved
exclusively for the world government.
From Inni's lobby, to Impel Down,
to Navy headquarters and back.
Think of it as a giant whirlpool
that connects those three facilities.
When the Gates of Justice are
opened at any of these locales,
usually to a Navy vessel?
Then the current from the whirlpool
changes and ships are ushered inside.
However, if the gates aren't opened,
the ship would keep following the
natural flow of the whirlpool.
Naturally,
most pirate ships would rather skip this
current altogether and go the long way.
Though it's convenient for the Navy.
What should I do then?
What do you want to do?
Don't tell me!
You have your brother's beaver card?
Uh, is that the moving paper
that you care so much about?
Nuh-uh, that one was a different one.
This is the card that Ace gave me.
They're also known as the paper of life,
since they give you a hint about
the person's state of health?
as well as their direction.
Then, if it's that small, that means...
Back when he first gave it to
me, it was ten times bigger.
Looks like Ace has been busy on his own
adventure.
It's perfectly natural for a guy
to worry about his bungling kid
brother.
Ace wouldn't be happy about
his little brother saving him,
but that's still better than him dying.
Either way, I'm gonna need
to take a little side trip.
Sorry everyone.
I have to save him.
He's the only brother I've got.
Perhaps you should think this through.
Do you have any idea how
reckless this plan is?
You're facing a full-fledged war.
You'll be nothing more than a
leaf whipped about by a storm,
an insect flicked away by hands
far mightier than your own.
Yeah, that doesn't matter to me.
I still gotta try.
I couldn't live with myself
if I let this happen.
I gotta do something.
Yes, I can see that.
So then, you plan to rescue the
most infamous prisoner in the world.
I give you a one in a
million chance of success.
But in order to even try, you need to get
to the great prison where he's being held.
Once they transport him to Marineford,
both the admirals and the warlords will
be keeping a close eye on the situation.
Keep in mind,
because your brother is the most
important prisoner in the Navy's custody,
the prison will be carefully guarded,
and it has quite the fearsome
reputation if you haven't heard.
It may prove impossible
to enter no matter what.
I'll worry about that when I get there.
There's no time now.
I gotta make it before they
take Ace to be executed.
Give me the biggest door you've
got, and I'll paddle like hell.
Now hold on a second.
You'll never reach the prison
by determination alone.
There is a slim chance this could work,
but the snake princess is
refusing to follow the order for
the seven warlords to assemble
But what if that changed?
If she obeyed that order,
we could take advantage of the situation
and sneak you on board their ship Wait,
what are you?
You mean there's a navy ship here?
Great, then I'm gonna go
ask her if she'll do it?
Greninion, it's terrible!
Inishida, what's all the fuss about?
Thank goodness I found you quickly
when I heard I came as fast as I could
Heard what?
It's awful.
The snake princess.
She's come down with a sickness.
And no one knows what it is?
Ah!
She's sick! Oh, no!
Whatever it is, fight it!
Don't give up.
Please stay strong.
What's this about the
snake princess falling ill?
Oh, Couran and Yon.
Man, I need you to wait outside.
What? But why?
I'm in a hurry! I knew that!
It hurts.
She keeps clutching her chest.
Perhaps something is wrong with her heart.
I've never seen anything like it.
Since her symptoms are a mystery,
there's very little I can
do in terms of treatment.
All we know is that
it's extremely painful.
She won't eat a thing and
she's hardly speaking either.
Tomorrow morning.
What are you doing?
Whatever it is, Granny
Nyon, you've got to stop it.
Yes, of course. That fool.
I should have realized.
It's a pity that the virus came
at a time like this. Huh? Virus?
If you know what it is, then just tell us.
I can't breathe, Granny Magellan.
Am I going to die like this?
Indeed, yes.
I'll say it isn't so.
If this is supposed to be
a joke, we're not laughing.
It has killed us before.
It took the life of our last Empress.
The same fate befell the
Empress before her, too.
I suffered from the illness myself, but
left the country before it took my life.
No remedy could save me
Snake princess monkey D.
Luffy has come to see you as well.
This is hardly the time He
has a request to ask of you.
Will you hear it?
What do you mean request?
Can't you see she's suffering?
How important could it be?
What just happened show him in quickly
Monkey D.
Luffy, you are a man favored by fate.
Perhaps this mountain
can be moved after all.
And perhaps you are the one to do it.
I hear you need something.
Yeah, I sure do.
But are you okay?
I heard you were sick.
Never mind that.
No illness can overtake me.
There's a pirate on
Whitebeard's crew named Ace.
He's my brother, and he's
about to be executed.
I gotta go rescue him.
But I heard if we took a
pirate ship, it'd be too slow.
So instead of going back to my friends,
I need you to get on a Navy
ship and take me with you.
How dare you even suggest
that, you selfish beast?
You know full well the
horrors our poor sister went
through and steal you a dragger
to that abhorrent prison?
How can you be so cruel?
This is exactly why we hate men.
We very well could have killed you,
but as soon as we show you mercy,
then you let it go to your head.
You're lucky she doesn't turn
you to stone and smash you.
You want me to follow the government's
orders and go with the other warlords?
He's said enough.
Strike him down.
If that is truly your request, then of
course, I will go anywhere you like.
Whoa, thanks. I was worried.
I don't know what I would
have done without your help.
She actually said yes.
She wouldn't listen to reason,
but she'll listen to him.
What happened to her, Granny?
Like the Empress before her,
our Empress succumbed to the burning
flames that are known only as love.
There's a saying in the East Blue
that describes these winds of passion.
Love is...
Always... A...
Moving on!